Guide to the Consumer Reports. Advocacy records, 1927-2011 and undated RL.11780
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Consumer Reports. Advocacy records
1927-2011 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Consumer Reports (Firm)
RL.11780
19.0 Linear Feet
Consumer Reports is a product testing and consumer advocacy nonprofit organization based in Yonkers, N.Y., founded in 1936. The Consumer Reports Advocacy records collection assembles materials relating to Consumer Reports' efforts at influencing public policy and addressing a variety of social issues. Materials originated at Consumer Reports main headquarters as well as at regional offices (Southwest Region, West Coast, Washington) more closely focused on advocacy activities. Materials include correspondence, press and publicity releases, clippings, research reports, policy papers, transcripts of testimony given before government and institutional agencies and committees, and other printed material. Social issues represented include antitrust investigations, automobile safety and rollover standards, child car seats, consumer credit, dairy products and food safety, household appliance safety, housing, insurance, lead poisoning, medical care, manufactured and mobile homes, mortgage bank practices, moving industry, pesticides, poverty, product liability, school lunch programs, steel and petroleum industry actions, telecommunications, and toy safety. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Arrangement
Organized into the following series: Administrative Files; Printed Materials; and Statements, Comments, Testimonies, etc.; and Consumer Policy Activities.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Consumer Reports. Advocacy records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2019.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
Advertising Council records
African American History Marketing and Promotional posters
Cause Marketing Forum Halo Awards records
Consumer Reports. Washington Office records
J. Walter Thompson Company. Detroit Office. Ford collateral literature
John Paver papers
Leonard Sirowitz papers
McCann Erickson Worldwide vertical files
Richard Pollay Tobacco Industry Promotion records
Collection Overview
The Consumer Reports Advocacy records collection assembles materials relating to Consumer Reports' efforts at influencing public policy and addressing a variety of social issues. Materials originated at Consumer Reports main headquarters as well as at regional offices (Southwest Region, West Coast, Washington) more closely focused on advocacy activities. Materials include correspondence, press and publicity releases, clippings, research reports, policy papers, transcripts of testimony given before government and institutional agencies and committees, and other printed material. Social issues represented include antitrust investigations, automobile safety and rollover standards, child car seats, consumer credit, dairy products and food safety, household appliance safety, housing, insurance, lead poisoning, medical care, manufactured and mobile homes, mortgage bank practices, moving industry, pesticides, poverty, product liability, school lunch programs, steel and petroleum industry actions, telecommunications, and toy safety. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
consumer protection; Public policy -- United States.; Antitrust investigations-United States; Automobiles -- United States; Credit; Food industry and trade -- United States; Household appliances, Electric; Insurance; Medical care; Mortgages -- United States; Petroleum; Poverty; Product safety; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
- Administrative Files, 1939-2007 and undated; 1
  - General Files, 1939-2005 and undated; 1
    - Administrative Division policies, 1974-1975 (Box 1)
    - CU Archives--Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1971-1981; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - CU Archives--Information pack, 1978 (Box 1)
    - CU Archives--NEH grant application, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Free CU web sites, 2005 (Box 1)
    - Gallup survey--Universal health care, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Gateway Productions (documentary), 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Health Care in Crisis--Media pack, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Index to Advocacy Office documents, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Online Shopper's Guide for Prescription Drugs, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Permission policy--Use of CU material, 1971-1974 (Box 1)
    - Project proposal--Chemical industry after Bhopal, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Project proposal--Preventing future Bhopals, 1987 (Box 1)
    - Project proposal--Sustainable agriculture in developing countries, 1991 (Box 1)
    - Proposal to ban Pharma crops, approximately 2002 (Box 1)
    - Proposed response to tobacco legislation, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Public information policy, 1971-1972; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Publications spreadsheet, undated (Box 1)
    - Southwest Regional Office--Community Reinvestment Act in Texas, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Southwest Regional Office--Work plan for 2002, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Subversive charges--American Legion report, 1954 (Box 1)
    - Washington Office--25th anniversary, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Washington Office--Guidelines, 1973 (Box 1)
    - West Coast Regional Office--1st annual meeting, 1939 (Box 1)
    - West Coast Regional Office--California contacts, 1974 (Box 1)
    - West Coast Regional Office--Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1972-19794 (Box 1)
    - West Coast Regional Office--Financial Information Bank for Refugees and Immigrants, 1990 (Box 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Booklets in Eastern Armenian, English, Farsi, Spanish, Vietnamese
    - West Coast Regional Office--Work plan for 2002, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Western Consumers Union--History, 1974; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Meetings and Conferences, 1986-2007; 2
    - Conference--Ending poverty, 1986 (Box 1)
    - Conference--FAO/Netherlands Conference on Agriculture and the Environment, 1991 (Box 1)
      United Nations Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO)
    - Conference--Health Care Summit, 2007 (Box 1)
    - Conference--IOCU (International Organization of Consumer Unions) Congress, 1987-1992 (Box 1)
      IOCU later renamed Consumers International
    - Conference--IOCU Consumer Policy Seminar, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Conference--Trust or Consequence (consumer trust in the Internet), 2005 (Box 1)
    - Consumer Web Watch Summit, 2002-2003 (Box 1)
    - Directors of advocacy offices, 1997-2001; 7 folders (Box 1)
    - Public Policy Leaders, 2002; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Public Policy Leaders, 2003-2004; 4 folders (Box 2)
  - Organizations, 1984-2003; 3
    - Center on Budget and Policy Priorities, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
    - Children's Defense Fund, 1987-1989 (Box 2)
    - Farmworkers, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Fenton Communications, 2003 (Box 2)
    - Jobs with Peace, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Justice for All, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Religious anti-poverty groups, 1984-1987; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Subject File, 1984-2002 and undated; 4
    - Arbitration, 2000 (Box 2)
    - Child safety seats, 1995 (Box 2)
    - Dry cleaning chemicals, 1995-2000 (Box 2)
    - Growth hormones (rgBH), 1993-1994 (Box 2)
    - Health, 1984-1987; 4 folders (Box 2)
    - Health, 1984-1987 (Box 16)
    - Health--Catastrophic health care, 1987-1988 (Box 2)
    - Health--Elderly, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Health--HMOs (Health Maintenance Organizations), 1987 (Box 2)
    - Health--Long-term care, 1984-1989; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Health--Medicaid, undated (Box 2)
    - Health--Medigap, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Health care, 1986-1989; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Health care reform, undated (Box 2)
    - Housing (binder), 1991 (Box 2)
    - Housing (binder), 1991; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Hunger, 1987 (Box 3)
    - Jobs, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
    - Manufactured/Mobile homes, 1997-2002 (Box 3)
    - Pesticides, undated (Box 3)
    - Poverty, 1985-1990; 4 folders (Box 3)
    - Poverty--Children, 1989-1992 (Box 3)
    - Poverty--International, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
    - Welfare, 1986-1987; 2 folders (Box 3)
- Printed Material, 1927-2011 and undated; 2
  - 2003 Guide to California's Medicare HMOs (Box 3)
  - A Golden Opportunity: Improving Children's Health Through California's Schools, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Advance Notice Regulatory Information Network newsletter, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
  - Advancing Accountability: A Tool for Transparent Foundation Grantmaking, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Affordability of Auto Insurance Among Low Income Families in Los Angeles, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Animal Factories: Pollution and Health Threats to Rural Texas, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Analysis of Pesticide Residue Data from the U.S. Department of Agriculture's Pesticide Data Program, 1994-1997 (Box 3)
  - Below the Line: Living Poor in America, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Best Buy Drugs (English and Spanish), 2005-2006 (Box 3)
  - Balancing Mission and Market: Nonprofits Walk a Tightrope Between the Public and Private Spheres, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Blueprint for Fair Share Health Care: Incremental Steps Toward Universal Health Care, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Books Consumerists (and others) Should Know About (Va. Tech Extension Division), 1980 (Box 3)
  - Breaking the Rules: AT&T's Attempt to Buy a National Monopoly in Cable TV and Broadband Internet Services, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Building and Maintaining Strong Foundations: Creating Community Responsive Philanthropy in Nonprofit Conversions, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Captive Kids: A Report on Commercial Pressures on Kids at School, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Catastrophic Illness Expenses (U.S. Department of Health and Human Services), 1986 (Box 3)
  - Code Blue: The Medi-Cal Emergency, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Consumer Guide to Handling Disputes with Your Employer or Private Health Plan, 2003, 2005; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Consumer Line newsletter, 1995-1996 (Box 3)
  - Consumer Reports Knows What's Best for Us All (Esquire magazine), 1974 (Box 3)
  - Consumer's Resource Handbook (U.S. Office of Consumer Affairs), 1990 (Box 3)
  - Consumer's Club Commodity List, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Consumerism at the Crossroads (Sentry Insurance), 1977; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Consumerism Problems from Consumers' Viewpoints (Center for Consumer Research), 1972 (Box 3)
  - Credit Insurance: The $2 Billion a Year Rip-Off, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Dirty Deeds: Abuses and Fraudulent Practices in California's Home Equity Market, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Do You Know What You're Eating? An Analysis of U.S. Government Data on Pesticide Residues in Foods, 1999 (Box 3)
  - DTV Made Easy (English and Spanish), approximately 2009 (Box 3)
  - Electronic Balance Transfer (EBT) Programs: Best Practices to Serve Recipients, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Encuentra la mejor universidad para ti (in Spanish), 2011 (Box 3)
  - Environmental Problems of Chemical Fertilizer Use, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Escape from the Pesticide Treadmill: Alternatives to Pesticides in Developing Countries, 1986-1987; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Evidence-based Medicine: Changing the Market with Consumer Information, 2005 (Box 3)
  - From the Ground Up: Grassroots Perspectives on Philanthropic Support for Health Reform, 2008 (Box 3)
  - Getting Action: How to Petition State Government, 1980 (Box 3)
  - Green Food Claims: An International Study of Self-declared Green Claims on Selected Food Products (Consumers International), 2004 (Box 3)
  - Guide to Documents of the Consumer Movement, 1980 (Box 3)
  - Guide to Income Tax, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Health Care Check-up: Consumers at Risk, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Health Care Crisis in the Latino Community, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Health Care Divide: Unfair Financial Burdens, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Health Care Security for All: The Single Payer Answer, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Hidden from View: The Growing Burden of Health Care Costs, 1998 (Box 4)
  - High Cost of Check Cashing, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Hospital Survey Kit, 1990 (Box 4)
  - How Good Are Your State's Nursing Homes?, 2003 (Box 4)
  - How Green Are You? An Environmental Impact Quiz, 1994 (Box 4)
  - In Over Our Heads: Consumers Report Predatory Lending and Fraud in Manufactured Housing, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Independent Review Organizations: Consumers Gain Needed Care When Unaffiliated Medical Experts Review Health Plan Denials, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Lessons from the 1996 Telecommunications Act: Deregulation Before Meaningful Competition Spells Consumer Disaster, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Letters to Congress: Consumers Union and Health Care Reform, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Life Support: Families Speak About Hospital, Hospice and Home Care for the Fatally Ill, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Long-Term Care: Analysis of Public Policy Options, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Low-Income Consumers: An Assessment of Current Issues and Programs, 1979 (Box 4)
  - Manage to Care: How California Can Better Inform Consumers About Managed Care, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Managed Care Consumers' Bill of Rights, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Medical Malpractice Insurance: Analysis of Alternative Policies, 1976 (Box 4)
  - Medical Savings Accounts: A Growing Threat to Consumers' Health Care Security, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Meeting Statutory Deadlines: Contractual and Financial Injury Litigation, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Memorandum for the Establishment of The Consumers Foundation, undated (Box 4)
  - Older American's Guide to Housing and Living Arrangements, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Pass H.R. 9 and S.430! End Insurance Price-Fixing, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Pay Phone Competition?, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Product Liability Fairness Act is Uniformly Unfair to Consumers, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Public Access to Public Courts: Discouraging Secrecy in the Public Interest (Texas Law Review), 1991 (Box 4)
  - Public Interest in the Conversions of Nonprofit Health Charities, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Rise of the Nanny State (Tom Holt; excerpt on CU), 1995 (Box 4)
  - Score Wars: The Case for Banning Use of Credit Information in Insurance, 2006 (Box 4)
  - Selling America's Kids: Commercial Pressures on Kids in the 90s, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Senator Edward M. Kennedy Report to Massachusetts, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Speaking Out: Consumers Union Key Health Care Testimony, 1994 (Box 4)
  - The American Dream: Opening the Door to Credit and Ending Mortgage Discrimination, 1993 (Box 4)
  - The Eyes Don't Have It. Yet. (Texas Contact Lens Prescription Act), 2001 (Box 4)
  - The Right Way to Spend California's 70 Billion Health Care Dollars (Health Access), 1991 (Box 4)
  - The Thin Red Line: How the Poor Still Pay More, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Upstairs, Downstairs: Percholorethylene in the Air in Apartments Above New York City Dry Cleaners, 1995 (Box 4)
  - What's Your Nutrition I.Q.?, 1977 (Box 4)
  - Workers as Consumers: How Consumers Union Serves Labor, undated (Box 4)
  - Worst First: High-Risk Insecticides, Children's Foods and Safer Alternatives, 1998 (Box 4)
- Statements, Comments, Testimonies, etc., 1954-2001 and undated; 3
  - Pre-1970, 1954-1969; 5
    - 5402001-0. Consumer-Farmer Milk Cooperative, 1954 (Box 5)
    - 6801001-0. Repair service fraud, 1968 (Box 5)
    - 6812001-1. Installment sales, 1968 (Box 5)
    - 6907001-0. Hearing aids, 1969 (Box 5)
  - 1970, 6
    - 7007001-0. Hearing aids, 1970 (Box 5)
    - 7012001-0. Toys, 1970 (Box 5)
    - 7012002-0. Toys, 1970 (Box 5)
    - 7012003-0. Toys, 1970 (Box 5)
    - 7012004-0. Toys, 1970 (Box 5)
  - 1971, 7
    - 7106001-0. Class actions, 1971 (Box 5)
    - 7107001-0. International trade, 1971 (Box 5)
    - 7112001-0. International trade, 1971 (Box 16)
    - 7112002-1. International trade, 1971 (Box 5)
  - 1972, 8
    - 7201001-0. Tomatoes, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7201002-1. Oil industry, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7202001-1. Oil and steel imports, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7203001-0. Meat imports, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7203002-1. Tobacco, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7204001-0. International trade, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7204002-0. Meat pricing, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7205001-1. Paper industry, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7205002-0. Steel imports, 1972 (Box 16)
    - 7205003-0. Steel imports, 1972 (Box 16)
    - 7206001-1. Oil industry, 1972 (Box 16)
    - 7206002-0. Litigation, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7206003-1. Oil industry, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7206004-1. Steel imports, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7207001-0. Automobile prices, 1972 (Box 16)
    - 7207002-0. Automobile prices, 1972 (Box 16)
    - 7207003-0. Automobile prices, 1972 (Box 16)
    - 7207004-0. Automobile prices, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7207005-1. Paper industry, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7208001-0. International trade, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7208002-0. International trade, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 72080003-1. Oil industry, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7208004-1. Oil industry, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7208005-0. Freedom of Information Act, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7209001-0. International trade, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7209002-0. Steel imports, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7209003-0. Steel imports, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7209004-0. Steel imports, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7209005-1. Activity report, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7210001-1. Oil industry, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7210002-1. Oil industry, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7211001-1. Moving industry, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7211002-1. Richard Frank, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7212001-1. International trade, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7212002-1. Oil industry, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7212003-1. Oil industry, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7212004-1. International trade, 1972 (Box 5)
  - 1973, 9
    - 7301001-1. Textiles, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7301002-0. Freedom of Information Act, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7301003-0. Bacon, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7301004-0. Bacon, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7302001-0. Steel imports, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7302002-1. Life insurance, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7302003-1. Tomatoes, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7303001-1. Oil imports, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7303003-1. Food, Drug and Cosmetic Act of 1938, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 7303004-1. Federal consumer protection, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7303005-0. Steel imports, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7303006-1. Food pricing, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7303007-1. Product warrantees, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7303008-0. Freedom of Information Act, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7304001-1. Natural gas, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7304002-0. Bacon, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7304003-0. CU data policy, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7305001-1. Class actions, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7305002-1. Class actions, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7305003-1. Class actions, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7305004-1. Antitrust--Toys, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7305005-1. Credit billing, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7305006-1. Health services, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7306001-0. Oil industry, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7306002-1. Moving industry, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7306003-1. Mattress flammability, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7306004-1. Drug advertising, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7306005-1. Drug advertising, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7306006-1. Meat industry, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7306007-1. Freedom of Information Act, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7306008-1. Periodical Correspondents Association, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7306009-1. Balloons, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7306010-0. Bacon, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7306011-0. Bacon, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7306012-0. CU v. Nissan, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7307001-1. Oil imports, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7307002-1. Oil imports, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7307003-1. Oil prices, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7307004-1. Toys, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7307005-1. Toys, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7307006-1. Food pricing, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7307007-1. Medical costs, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7307008-1. Appliance labeling for energy conservation, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7307009-1. Balloons, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7307010-1. Balloons, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7307011-1. Balloons, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7307012-0. Analgesics, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7307013-0. Analgesics, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7307014-0. Bacon, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7308001-1. Oil imports, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7308002-1. Freedom of Information Act, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7308003-1. Public utilities, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7308004-1. Food pricing, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7308005-1. Health care costs, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7308006-1. Balloons, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7308007-1. Balloons, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7309001-1. Meat inspection, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7309002-1. Adhesives, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7309003-1. Federal consumer protection, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7309004-1. Animal testing--Drugs, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7309005-1. Moving industry, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7309006-1. Toys, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7309007-1. Balloons, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7309008-1. Balloons, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7310001-1. Class actions, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7310002-1. Class actions, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7310003-1. Class actions, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7310004-1. Class actions, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7310005-1. Price increases, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7310006-1. Natural gas, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7310007-1. Cost of Living Council, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7310008-1. Bank accounts, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7311001-1. Cable television, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7311002-1. Pedal-powered vehicles, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7311003-1. Natural gas, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7311004-1. Automobile prices, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7311005-1. Balloons, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7311006-1. Federal consumer protection, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7311007-1. Commercial banks, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7311008-1. Lead in milk products, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7312001-1. Trucking industry, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7312002-1. Turtles, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7312003-1. Turtles, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7312005-1. Toys, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7312006-1. Health care costs, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7312007-1. Public utilities, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 7312008-1. Textile imports, 1973 (Box 16)
    - 7312009-1. Rehabilitation equipment, 1973 (Box 5)
  - 1974, 10
    - 7401001-1. Turtles, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7401002-1. Public utilities, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7401003-1. Health care costs, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7401004-1. Air transport, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7401005-1. Child automobile restraints, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7401006-1. Child automobile restraints, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7401007-1. Child automobile restraints, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7401008-1. Health services, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7401009-1. Savings bank life insurance, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7401010-1. Life insurance, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7401011-1. Alcoholic beverages, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7401012-1. Pets, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7401013-1. Balloons, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7401014-1. Balloons, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7401015-0. Baby cribs, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7401016-1. Business, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7401017-1. Conflict of interest, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7402001-1. Balloons, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7402002-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7402003-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7402004-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7402005-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7402006-1. Natural gas, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7402007-1. Natural gas, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7402008-1. Natural gas, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7402009-1. Product safety standards, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7402010-1. Food inspection, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7402011-0. Television broadcasting, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7402012-0. Television broadcasting, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7402013-0. Television broadcasting, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7402014-1. Natural gas, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7402015-0. Economics, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7402016-1. Bank accounts, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7402017-1. Balloons, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7402018-1. Drug advertising, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7402019-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7403001-1. Business, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7403002-1. Business, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7403003-1. Business, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7403004-1. Business, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7403005-1. Toys, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7403006-1. Automobile fuel economy, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7403007-1. Small claims courts, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7403008-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7403009-1. Adhesives, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7403010-1. Frozen food, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7403011-1. Textile flammability, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7403012-1. Nursing homes, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7403013-1. Drained food weights, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7403014-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1974 (Box 16)
    - 7403015-1. Air conditioners, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7403016-1. Life insurance, 1974 (Box 5)
    - 7403017-1. Credit cards, 1974 (Box 6)
    - 7403018-2. Consumers Union in California, 1974 (Box 16)